{
  "chapter": 12,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following design principles does SOA promote?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Low coupling",
        "High coupling",
        "Low cohesion",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which element of a service remains hidden from the consumers?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Contract",
        "Interface",
        "Implementation",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Cloud computing and SOA can run separately but together they empower one another.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Benefits of using SOA paradigm include",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Easier maintenance",
        "Increased flexibility",
        "Reduced cost",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Service registry in SOA paradigm is maintained by",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Service provider",
        "Service broker",
        "Service consumer",
        "Service designer"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Connection between services in SOA paradigm is done through",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Message passing",
        "Remote method invocation",
        "Functional call",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Use of variety of technologies for application development across heterogeneous systems in cloud computing makes the interoperation among the applications quite challenging without properly",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Designed system",
        "Standardized communication",
        "Open-source implementation",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Technological inter-dependency of two communication software agents in SOA paradigm has been eliminated by",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use of SOAP",
        "Use of service registry",
        "Standardized message communication technique",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "In cloud computing, SOA paradigm is used to",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Build dynamic cloud infrastructure",
        "Deliver the services",
        "Build the application",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Service contract once published should not be changed ever because",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Provider can never know who are already using the service",
        "It is a complex task",
        "Service implementation is unalterable",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}
